export const ssQuestions = [
  {
    checkbox: "ques_1",
    problem: "Set Matrix Zeroes",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/set-matrix-zeroes/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/N0MgLvceX7M",
    codingNinja:
      "https://www.codingninjas.com/codestudio/problems/set-matrix-zeros_3846774?topList=striver-sde-sheet-problems&utm_source=striver&utm_medium=website",
    topicNo: 0,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_2",
    problem: "Pascal's Triangle",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/pascals-triangle/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/bR7mQgwQ_o8",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3rhv153",
    topicNo: 0,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_3",
    problem: "Next Permutation",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/next-permutation/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/JDOXKqF60RQ",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3qoj5iQ",
    topicNo: 0,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_4",
    problem: "Kadane's Algorithm",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/maximum-subarray/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/AHZpyENo7k4",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3HZltTa",
    topicNo: 0,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_5",
    problem: "Sort an array of 0’s 1’s 2’s",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/sort-colors/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/tp8JIuCXBaU",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3tlM60B",
    topicNo: 0,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_6",
    problem: "Stock buy and Sell",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/best-time-to-buy-and-sell-stock/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/excAOvwF_Wk",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3GsANaD",
    topicNo: 0,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_7",
    problem: "Rotate Matrix",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/rotate-image/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/Z0R2u6gd3GU",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3rhVUWx",
    topicNo: 1,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_8",
    problem: "Merge Overlapping Subintervals",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/merge-intervals/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/IexN60k62jo",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3rj9LvO",
    topicNo: 1,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_9",
    problem: "Merge two sorted Arrays without extra space",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/merge-sorted-array/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/n7uwj04E0I4",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/33umm7e",
    topicNo: 1,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_10",
    problem: "Find the duplicate in an array of N+1 integers",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/find-the-duplicate-number/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/32Ll35mhWg0",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3GtKDJb",
    topicNo: 1,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_11",
    problem: "Repeat and Missing Number",
    leetCode:
      "https://www.interviewbit.com/problems/repeat-and-missing-number-array/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/2D0D8HE6uak}",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3Gs6wZu",
    topicNo: 1,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_12",
    problem: "Inversion of Array (Pre-req: Merge Sort)",
    leetCode:
      "https://www.codingninjas.com/codestudio/problems/count-inversions_615",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/AseUmwVNaoY",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/339fFb7",
    topicNo: 1,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_13",
    problem: "Search in a 2d Matrix",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/search-a-2d-matrix/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/ZYpYur0znng",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3GD7NNa",
    topicNo: 2,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_14",
    problem: "Pow(X,n)",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/powx-n/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/l0YC3876qxg",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3Gtjwhl",
    topicNo: 2,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_15",
    problem: "Majority Element (>N/2 times)",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/majority-element/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/nP_ns3uSh80",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3FpfpBQ",
    topicNo: 2,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_16",
    problem: "Majority Element (>N/3 times)",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/majority-element-ii/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/vwZj1K0e9U8",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3foYLYp",
    topicNo: 2,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_17",
    problem: "Grid Unique Paths",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/unique-paths/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/t_f0nwwdg5o}",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3fm1dyN",
    topicNo: 2,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_18",
    problem: "Reverse Pairs (Leetcode)",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/reverse-pairs/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/0e4bZaP3MDI}",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3tm5PgF",
    topicNo: 2,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_19",
    problem: "2-Sum-Problem",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/two-sum/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/UXDSeD9mN-k",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3riXBmz",
    topicNo: 3,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_20",
    problem: "4-sum-Problem",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/4sum/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/eD95WRfh81c",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3qpfEsj",
    topicNo: 3,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_21",
    problem: "Longest Consecutive Sequence",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/longest-consecutive-sequence/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/oO5uLE7EUlM",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/34EoAS0",
    topicNo: 3,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_22",
    problem: "Largest Subarray with K sum",
    leetCode:
      "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/largest-subarray-with-0-sum/1",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/frf7qxiN2qU}",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/31UHoeM",
    topicNo: 3,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_23",
    problem: "Count number of subarrays with given Xor K",
    leetCode: "https://www.interviewbit.com/problems/subarray-with-given-xor/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/eZr-6p0B7ME",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3fp24yN",
    topicNo: 3,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_24",
    problem: "Longest Substring without repeat",
    leetCode:
      "https://leetcode.com/problems/longest-substring-without-repeating-characters/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/qtVh-XEpsJo",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3no44fb",
    topicNo: 3,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_25",
    problem: "Reverse a LinkedList",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/reverse-linked-list/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/iRtLEoL-r-g",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3qoE6K6",
    topicNo: 4,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_26",
    problem: "Find the middle of LinkedList",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/middle-of-the-linked-list/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/sGdwSH8RK-o",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3KcRxoG",
    topicNo: 4,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_27",
    problem: "Merge two sorted Linked List (use method used in mergeSort)",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/merge-two-sorted-lists/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/Xb4slcp1U38",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3qnbSj8",
    topicNo: 4,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_28",
    problem: "Remove N-th node from back of LinkedList",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/remove-nth-node-from-end-of-list/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/Lhu3MsXZy-Q",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3riZ4JB",
    topicNo: 4,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_29",
    problem: "Add two numbers as LinkedList",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/add-two-numbers/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/LBVsXSMOIk4",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3qqbgcq",
    topicNo: 4,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_30",
    problem: "Delete a given Node when a node is given.(0(1) solution)",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/delete-node-in-a-linked-list/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/icnp4FJdZ_c",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3GqW4kN",
    topicNo: 4,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_31",
    problem: "Find intersection point of Y LinkedList",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/intersection-of-two-linked-lists/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/u4FWXfgS8jw",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3fiMQeG",
    topicNo: 5,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_32",
    problem: "Detect a cycle in Linked List",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/linked-list-cycle/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/354J83hX7RI",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3I2fmxh",
    topicNo: 5,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_33",
    problem: "Reverse a LinkedList in groups of size k.",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/reverse-nodes-in-k-group/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/Of0HPkk3JgI",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3Gsfk1u",
    topicNo: 5,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_34",
    problem: "Check if a LinkedList is palindrome or not.",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/palindrome-linked-list/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/-DtNInqFUXs",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3GqRMKv",
    topicNo: 5,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_35",
    problem: "Find the starting point of the Loop of LinkedList",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/linked-list-cycle-ii/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/QfbOhn0WZ88",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3K32lpf",
    topicNo: 5,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_36",
    problem: "Flattening of a LinkedList",
    leetCode:
      "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/flattening-a-linked-list/1",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/ysytSSXpAI0",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3nqtEA1",
    topicNo: 5,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_37",
    problem: "Rotate a LinkedList",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/rotate-list/description/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/9VPm6nEbVPA",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/33bNQPo",
    topicNo: 6,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_38",
    problem: "Clone a Linked List with random and next pointer",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/copy-list-with-random-pointer/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/VNf6VynfpdM",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3qnFoFg",
    topicNo: 6,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_39",
    problem: "3 sum",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/3sum/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/onLoX6Nhvmg",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/33wlWxk",
    topicNo: 6,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_40",
    problem: "Trapping rainwater",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/trapping-rain-water/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/m18Hntz4go8",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3KcxExJ",
    topicNo: 6,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_41",
    problem: "Remove Duplicate from Sorted array",
    leetCode:
      "https://leetcode.com/problems/remove-duplicates-from-sorted-array/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/Fm_p9lJ4Z_8",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/31Usllh",
    topicNo: 6,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_42",
    problem: "Max consecutive ones",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/max-consecutive-ones/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/Mo33MjjMlyA",
    codingNinja: "https://leetcode.com/problems/max-consecutive-ones/",
    topicNo: 6,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_43",
    problem: "N meetings in one room",
    leetCode:
      "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/n-meetings-in-one-room-1587115620/1",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/II6ziNnub1Q",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3zXdqn5",
    topicNo: 7,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_44",
    problem: "Minimum number of platforms required for a railway",
    leetCode:
      "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/minimum-platforms-1587115620/1#",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/dxVcMDI7vyI",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3npx0mW",
    topicNo: 7,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_45",
    problem: "Job sequencing Problem",
    leetCode:
      "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/job-sequencing-problem-1587115620/1#",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/LjPx4wQaRIs",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3K9XZfV",
    topicNo: 7,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_46",
    problem: "Fractional Knapsack Problem",
    leetCode:
      "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/fractional-knapsack-1587115620/1",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/F_DDzYnxO14",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3I7fNXn",
    topicNo: 7,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_47",
    problem: "Greedy algorithm to find minimum number of coins",
    leetCode:
      "https://www.geeksforgeeks.org/find-minimum-number-of-coins-that-make-a-change/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/mVg9CfJvayM",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3nquVHj",
    topicNo: 7,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_48",
    problem: "Activity Selection (it is the same as N meeting in one room)",
    leetCode:
      "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/n-meetings-in-one-room-1587115620/1",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/II6ziNnub1Q",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3I2iPvN",
    topicNo: 7,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_49",
    problem: "Subset Sums",
    leetCode: "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/subset-sums2234/1",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/rYkfBRtMJr8",
    codingNinja:
      "https://www.codingninjas.com/codestudio/problems/subset-sum_3843086?topList=striver-sde-sheet-problems&utm_source=striver&utm_medium=website",
    topicNo: 8,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_50",
    problem: "Subset-II",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/subsets-ii/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/RIn3gOkbhQE",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3qnaLjq",
    topicNo: 8,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_51",
    problem: "Combination sum-1",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/combination-sum/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/OyZFFqQtu98",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3qpmDS1",
    topicNo: 8,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_52",
    problem: "Combination sum-2",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/combination-sum-ii/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/G1fRTGRxXU8",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3tkbtjk",
    topicNo: 8,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_53",
    problem: "Palindrome Partitioning",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/palindrome-partitioning/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/WBgsABoClE0",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3HZPNgs",
    topicNo: 8,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_54",
    problem: "K-th permutation Sequence",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/permutation-sequence/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/wT7gcXLYoao",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3KcCP0D",
    topicNo: 8,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_55",
    problem: "Print all permutations of a string/array",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/permutations/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/f2ic2Rsc9pU",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3fmwxNV",
    topicNo: 9,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_56",
    problem: "N queens Problem",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/n-queens/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/i05Ju7AftcM",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3zSZavC",
    topicNo: 9,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_57",
    problem: "Sudoku Solver",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/sudoku-solver/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/FWAIf_EVUKE",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/31Z5Iwe",
    topicNo: 9,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_58",
    problem: "M coloring Problem",
    leetCode:
      "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/m-coloring-problem-1587115620/1#",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/wuVwUK25Rfc",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3I48oI6",
    topicNo: 9,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_59",
    problem: "Rat in a Maze",
    leetCode:
      "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/rat-in-a-maze-problem/1",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/bLGZhJlt4y0",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3fmwP7t",
    topicNo: 9,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_60",
    problem: "Word Break (print all ways)",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3FxgW92",
    topicNo: 9,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_61",
    problem: "The N-th root of an integer",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/WjpswYrS2nY",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3rj7Ib1",
    topicNo: 10,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_62",
    problem: "Matrix Median",
    leetCode: "https://www.interviewbit.com/problems/matrix-median/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/63fPPOdIr2c",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/33AHZTz",
    topicNo: 10,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_63",
    problem:
      "Find the element that appears once in a sorted array, and the rest element appears twice (Binary search)",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/single-element-in-a-sorted-array/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/PzszoiY5XMQ",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3rng2qC",
    topicNo: 10,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_64",
    problem:
      "Search element in a sorted and rotated array/ find pivot where it is rotated",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/search-in-rotated-sorted-array/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/r3pMQ8-Ad5s",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3nnxGcm",
    topicNo: 10,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_65",
    problem: "Median of 2 sorted arrays",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/median-of-two-sorted-arrays/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/NTop3VTjmxk",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3Ka3jQr",
    topicNo: 10,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_66",
    problem: "K-th element of two sorted arrays",
    leetCode:
      "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/k-th-element-of-two-sorted-array1317/1",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/nv7F4PiLUzo",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3qm0cgu",
    topicNo: 10,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_67",
    problem: "Allocate Minimum Number of Pages",
    leetCode: "https://www.interviewbit.com/problems/allocate-books/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/gYmWHvRHu-s",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3FrKxk7",
    topicNo: 10,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_68",
    problem: "Aggressive Cows",
    leetCode: "https://www.spoj.com/problems/AGGRCOW/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/wSOfYesTBRk",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3zV52ob",
    topicNo: 10,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_69",
    problem: "Max heap, Min Heap Implementation (Only for interviews)",
    codingNinja:
      "https://www.codingninjas.com/codestudio/problems/min-heap_4691801?topList=striver-sde-sheet-problems&utm_source=striver&utm_medium=website",
    topicNo: 11,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_70",
    problem: "Kth Largest Element",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/kth-largest-element-in-an-array/",
    codingNinja:
      "https://www.codingninjas.com/codestudio/problems/kth-smallest-and-largest-element-of-array_1115488?topList=striver-sde-sheet-problems&utm_source=striver&utm_medium=website",
    topicNo: 11,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_71",
    problem: "Maximum Sum Combination",
    leetCode: "https://www.interviewbit.com/problems/maximum-sum-combinations/",
    codingNinja:
      "https://www.codingninjas.com/codestudio/problems/k-max-sum-combinations_975322?topList=striver-sde-sheet-problems&utm_source=striver&utm_medium=website",
    topicNo: 11,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_72",
    problem: "Find Median from Data Stream",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/find-median-from-data-stream/",
    codingNinja:
      "https://www.codingninjas.com/codestudio/problems/running-median_625409?topList=striver-sde-sheet-problems&utm_source=striver&utm_medium=website",
    topicNo: 11,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_73",
    problem: "Merge K sorted arrays",
    leetCode:
      "https://www.codingninjas.com/codestudio/problems/merge-k-sorted-arrays_975379",
    codingNinja:
      "https://www.codingninjas.com/codestudio/problems/merge-k-sorted-arrays_975379?topList=striver-sde-sheet-problems&utm_source=striver&utm_medium=website",
    topicNo: 11,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_74",
    problem: "K most frequent elements",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/top-k-frequent-elements/",
    codingNinja:
      "https://www.codingninjas.com/codestudio/problems/k-most-frequent-elements_3167808?topList=striver-sde-sheet-problems&utm_source=striver&utm_medium=website",
    topicNo: 11,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_75",
    problem: "Implement Stack Using Arrays",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/GYptUgnIM_I",
    codingNinja:
      "https://www.codingninjas.com/codestudio/problems/stack-implementation-using-array_3210209",
    topicNo: 12,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_76",
    problem: "Implement Queue Using Arrays",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/M6GnoUDpqEE",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3KbIjIW",
    topicNo: 12,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_77",
    problem: "Implement Stack using Queue (using single queue)",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/implement-stack-using-queues/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/jDZQKzEtbYQ",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3reLgQs",
    topicNo: 12,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_78",
    problem: "Implement Queue using Stack (0(1) amortized method)",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/implement-queue-using-stacks/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/3Et9MrMc02A",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3reLeIk",
    topicNo: 12,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_79",
    problem: "Check for balanced parentheses",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/valid-parentheses/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/wkDfsKijrZ8",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3nr1RiO",
    topicNo: 12,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_80",
    problem: "Next Greater Element",
    leetCode:
      "https://leetcode.com/problems/next-greater-element-ii/description/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/Du881K7Jtk8",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3qyCjCF",
    topicNo: 12,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_81",
    problem: "Sort a Stack",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3nptF7k",
    topicNo: 12,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_82",
    problem: "Next Smaller Element",
    leetCode: "https://www.interviewbit.com/problems/nearest-smaller-element/",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3K6WVtb",
    topicNo: 13,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_83",
    problem: "LRU cache (IMPORTANT)",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/lru-cache/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/xDEuM5qa0zg",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3K7Cs7I",
    topicNo: 13,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_84",
    problem: "LFU Cache",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/lfu-cache/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/0PSB9y8ehbk",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3noxuK0",
    topicNo: 13,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_85",
    problem: "Largest rectangle in a histogram",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/largest-rectangle-in-histogram/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/X0X6G-eWgQ8",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3qpxbR9",
    topicNo: 13,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_86",
    problem: "Sliding Window maximum",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/sliding-window-maximum/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/CZQGRp93K4k",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3GmTkoC",
    topicNo: 13,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_87",
    problem: "Implement Min Stack",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/min-stack/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/V09NfaGf2ao}",
    codingNinja:
      "https://www.codingninjas.com/codestudio/problems/min-stack_3843991?topList=striver-sde-sheet-problems&utm_source=striver&utm_medium=website",
    topicNo: 13,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_88",
    problem: "Rotten Orange (Using BFS)",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/rotting-oranges/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/yf3oUhkvqA0",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/33zH0TC",
    topicNo: 13,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_89",
    problem: "Stock Span Problem",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/online-stock-span/",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3GvBtMk",
    topicNo: 13,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_90",
    problem: "Find the maximum of minimums of every window size",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3zUYLZz",
    topicNo: 13,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_91",
    problem: "The Celebrity Problem",
    leetCode:
      "https://leetcode.com/accounts/login/?next=/problems/find-the-celebrity/",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3GuImxi",
    topicNo: 13,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_92",
    problem: "Reverse Words in a String",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/reverse-words-in-a-string/",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3FmKc1X",
    topicNo: 14,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_93",
    problem: "Longest Palindrome in a string",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/longest-palindromic-substring/",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3Grdrlv",
    topicNo: 14,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_94",
    problem: "Roman Number to Integer and vice versa",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/roman-to-integer/",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3rkGuBb",
    topicNo: 14,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_95",
    problem: "Implement ATOI/STRSTR",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/string-to-integer-atoi/",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3zXpYeb",
    topicNo: 14,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_96",
    problem: "Longest Common Prefix",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/longest-common-prefix/",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3GlNN1D",
    topicNo: 14,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_97",
    problem: "Rabin Karp",
    leetCode:
      "https://leetcode.com/problems/repeated-string-match/discuss/416144/Rabin-Karp-algorithm-C%2B%2B-implementation",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3FvnLaN",
    topicNo: 14,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_98",
    problem: "Z-Function",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/implement-strstr/",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3qs24UM",
    topicNo: 15,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_99",
    problem: "KMP algo / LPS(pi) array",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/implement-strstr/",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/31VF1s6",
    topicNo: 15,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_100",
    problem:
      "Minimum characters needed to be inserted in the beginning to make it palindromic",
    leetCode:
      "https://www.interviewbit.com/problems/minimum-characters-required-to-make-a-string-palindromic/",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/34RE855",
    topicNo: 15,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_101",
    problem: "Check for Anagrams",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/valid-anagram/",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3K6weoJ",
    topicNo: 15,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_102",
    problem: "Count and Say",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/count-and-say/",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3K8Uwyi",
    topicNo: 15,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_103",
    problem: "Compare version numbers",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/compare-version-numbers/",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3GwYuys",
    topicNo: 15,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_104",
    problem: "Inorder Traversal",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/binary-tree-inorder-traversal/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/Z_NEgBgbRVI",
    topicNo: 16,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_105",
    problem: "Preorder Traversal",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/binary-tree-preorder-traversal/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/RlUu72JrOCQ}",
    topicNo: 16,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_106",
    problem: "Postorder Traversal",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/binary-tree-postorder-traversal/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/COQOU6klsBg}",
    topicNo: 16,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_107",
    problem: "Morris Inorder Traversal",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/binary-tree-inorder-traversal/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/80Zug6D1_r4",
    topicNo: 16,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_108",
    problem: "Morris Preorder Traversal",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/80Zug6D1_r4}",
    topicNo: 16,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_109",
    problem: "LeftView Of Binary Tree",
    leetCode:
      "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/left-view-of-binary-tree/1",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/KV4mRzTjlAk",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3GtxyQa",
    topicNo: 16,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_110",
    problem: "Bottom View of Binary Tree",
    leetCode:
      "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/bottom-view-of-binary-tree/1",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/0FtVY6I4pB8",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3trqFLq",
    topicNo: 16,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_111",
    problem: "Top View of Binary Tree",
    leetCode:
      "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/top-view-of-binary-tree/1",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/Et9OCDNvJ78",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3Gs76WV",
    topicNo: 16,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_112",
    problem: "Preorder inorder postorder in a single traversal",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/ySp2epYvgTE}",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3rlXpTX",
    topicNo: 16,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_113",
    problem: "Vertical order traversal",
    leetCode:
      "https://leetcode.com/problems/vertical-order-traversal-of-a-binary-tree/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/q_a6lpbKJdw}",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3KaM41v",
    topicNo: 16,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_114",
    problem: "Root to node path in a Binary Tree",
    leetCode: "https://www.interviewbit.com/problems/path-to-given-node/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/fmflMqVOC7k}",
    topicNo: 16,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_115",
    problem: "Max width of a Binary Tree",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/maximum-width-of-binary-tree/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/ZbybYvcVLks}",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3rm014d",
    topicNo: 16,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_116",
    problem: "Level order Traversal / Level order traversal in spiral form",
    leetCode:
      "https://leetcode.com/problems/binary-tree-level-order-traversal/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/EoAsWbO7sqg}",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3zVtSnX",
    topicNo: 17,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_117",
    problem: "Height of a Binary Tree",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/maximum-depth-of-binary-tree/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/eD3tmO66aBA}",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3qoOEco",
    topicNo: 17,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_118",
    problem: "Diameter of Binary Tree",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/diameter-of-binary-tree/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/Rezetez59Nk}",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3I3O1uD",
    topicNo: 17,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_119",
    problem: "Check if the Binary tree is height-balanced or not",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/balanced-binary-tree/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/Yt50Jfbd8Po}",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3fqsvnA",
    topicNo: 17,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_120",
    problem: "LCA in Binary Tree",
    leetCode:
      "https://leetcode.com/problems/lowest-common-ancestor-of-a-binary-tree/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/_-QHfMDde90}",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3tqcRko",
    topicNo: 17,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_121",
    problem: "Check if two trees are identical or not",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/same-tree/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/BhuvF_-PWS0}",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3GuQYnE",
    topicNo: 17,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_122",
    problem: "Zig Zag Traversal of Binary Tree",
    leetCode:
      "https://leetcode.com/problems/binary-tree-zigzag-level-order-traversal/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/3OXWEdlIGl4}",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3GrS3g7",
    topicNo: 17,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_123",
    problem: "Boundary Traversal of Binary Tree",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/boundary-of-binary-tree/#",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/0ca1nvR0be4}",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3GxQ6yH",
    topicNo: 17,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_124",
    problem: "Maximum path sum",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/binary-tree-maximum-path-sum/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/WszrfSwMz58}",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3rkQUR4",
    topicNo: 18,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_125",
    problem: "Construct Binary Tree from inorder and preorder",
    leetCode:
      "https://leetcode.com/problems/construct-binary-tree-from-preorder-and-inorder-traversal/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/aZNaLrVebKQ}",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3fqOif3",
    topicNo: 18,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_126",
    problem: "Construct Binary Tree from Inorder and Postorder",
    leetCode:
      "https://leetcode.com/problems/construct-binary-tree-from-inorder-and-postorder-traversal/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/LgLRTaEMRVc}",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3qrzumM",
    topicNo: 18,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_127",
    problem: "Symmetric Binary Tree",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/symmetric-tree/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/nKggNAiEpBE}",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3GItN9P",
    topicNo: 18,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_128",
    problem: "Flatten Binary Tree to LinkedList",
    leetCode:
      "https://leetcode.com/problems/flatten-binary-tree-to-linked-list/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/sWf7k1x9XR4}",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3qA9uWt",
    topicNo: 18,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_129",
    problem: "Check if Binary Tree is the mirror of itself or not",
    leetCode: "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/mirror-tree/1",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3nqSnnQ",
    topicNo: 18,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_130",
    problem: "Check for Children Sum Property",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/fnmisPM6cVo}",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/33yExIQ",
    topicNo: 18,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_131",
    problem: "Populate Next Right pointers of Tree",
    leetCode:
      "https://leetcode.com/problems/populating-next-right-pointers-in-each-node/",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/33Bm8uX",
    topicNo: 19,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_132",
    problem: "Search given Key in BST",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/search-in-a-binary-search-tree/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/KcNt6v_56cc}",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3Ft26jR",
    topicNo: 19,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_133",
    problem: "Construct BST from given keys",
    leetCode:
      "https://leetcode.com/problems/convert-sorted-array-to-binary-search-tree/",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3qr5I1t",
    topicNo: 19,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_134",
    problem: "Construct BST from preorder traversal",
    leetCode:
      "https://leetcode.com/problems/construct-binary-search-tree-from-preorder-traversal/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/UmJT3j26t1I}",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3Fr7GTQ",
    topicNo: 19,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_135",
    problem: "Check is a BT is BST or not",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/validate-binary-search-tree/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/f-sj7I5oXEI}",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3nmKek7",
    topicNo: 19,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_136",
    problem: "Find LCA of two nodes in BST",
    leetCode:
      "https://leetcode.com/problems/lowest-common-ancestor-of-a-binary-search-tree/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/cX_kPV_foZc}",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3qqoaXM",
    topicNo: 19,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_137",
    problem: "Find the inorder predecessor/successor of a given Key in BST.",
    leetCode:
      "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/predecessor-and-successor/1",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/SXKAD2svfmI}",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3A0hm6l",
    topicNo: 19,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_138",
    problem: "Floor in a BST",
    leetCode:
      "https://www.codingninjas.com/codestudio/problems/floor-from-bst_920457?source=youtube&campaign=Striver_Tree_Videos&utm_source=youtube&utm_medium=affiliate&utm_campaign=Striver_Tree_Videos",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/xm_W1ub-K-w",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3nsqdbY",
    topicNo: 20,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_139",
    problem: "Ceil in a BST",
    leetCode:
      "https://www.codingninjas.com/codestudio/problems/ceil-from-bst_920464?source=youtube&campaign=Striver_Tree_Videos&utm_source=youtube&utm_medium=affiliate&utm_campaign=Striver_Tree_Videos",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/KSsk8AhdOZA",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/33b9enW",
    topicNo: 20,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_140",
    problem: "Find K-th smallest element in BST",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/kth-smallest-element-in-a-bst/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/9TJYWh0adfk}",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3rf0HrP",
    topicNo: 20,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_141",
    problem: "Find K-th largest element in BST",
    leetCode:
      "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/kth-largest-element-in-bst/1",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/9TJYWh0adfk}",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/31Yjtet",
    topicNo: 20,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_142",
    problem: "Find a pair with a given sum in BST",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/two-sum-iv-input-is-a-bst/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/ssL3sHwPeb4}",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3FvDAOO",
    topicNo: 20,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_143",
    problem: "BST iterator",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/binary-search-tree-iterator/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/D2jMcmxU4bs}",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3FsH5FC",
    topicNo: 20,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_144",
    problem: "Size of the largest BST in a Binary Tree",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/maximum-sum-bst-in-binary-tree/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/X0oXMdtUDwo}",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3fn6h5V",
    topicNo: 20,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_145",
    problem: "Serialize and deserialize Binary Tree",
    leetCode:
      "https://leetcode.com/problems/serialize-and-deserialize-binary-tree/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/-YbXySKJsX8",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3qr6pYD",
    topicNo: 20,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_146",
    problem: "Binary Tree to Double Linked List",
    leetCode:
      "https://leetcode.com/problems/flatten-binary-tree-to-linked-list/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/sWf7k1x9XR4",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3HVnGz0",
    topicNo: 21,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_147",
    problem: "Find median in a stream of running integers.",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/find-median-from-data-stream/",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3rkTB58",
    topicNo: 21,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_148",
    problem: "K-th largest element in a stream.",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/kth-largest-element-in-a-stream/",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3KdiUPp",
    topicNo: 21,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_149",
    problem: "Distinct numbers in Window.",
    leetCode:
      "https://www.interviewbit.com/problems/distinct-numbers-in-window/",
    codingNinja:
      "https://www.codingninjas.com/codestudio/problems/920336?topList=striver-sde-sheet-problems&utm_source=striver&utm_medium=website",
    topicNo: 21,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_150",
    problem: "K-th largest element in an unsorted array.",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/kth-largest-element-in-an-array/",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3GvQttz",
    topicNo: 21,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_151",
    problem: "Flood-fill Algorithm",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/flood-fill/",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3Gv1Th5",
    topicNo: 21,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_152",
    problem: "Clone a graph (Not that easy as it looks)",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/clone-graph/",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/33BcVmE",
    topicNo: 22,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_153",
    problem: "DFS",
    leetCode:
      "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/depth-first-traversal-for-a-graph/1",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/Qzf1a--rhp8}",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/33BcXeg",
    topicNo: 22,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_154",
    problem: "BFS",
    leetCode:
      "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/bfs-traversal-of-graph/1",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/-tgVpUgsQ5k}",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3rgb26U",
    topicNo: 22,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_155",
    problem: "Detect A cycle in Undirected Graph using BFS",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/course-schedule/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/BPlrALf1LDU}",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3npFdrn",
    topicNo: 22,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_156",
    problem: "Detect A cycle in Undirected Graph using DFS",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/course-schedule/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/zQ3zgFypzX4}",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3npFdrn",
    topicNo: 22,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_157",
    problem: "Detect A cycle in a Directed Graph using DFS",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/course-schedule/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/uzVUw90ZFIg",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3FrzaZp",
    topicNo: 22,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_158",
    problem: "Detect A cycle in a Directed Graph using BFS",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/course-schedule/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/iTBaI90lpDQ",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3FrzaZp",
    topicNo: 22,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_159",
    problem: "Topological Sort BFS",
    leetCode: "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/topological-sort/1",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/73sneFXuTEg",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/33bapUo",
    topicNo: 22,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_160",
    problem: "Topological Sort DFS",
    leetCode: "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/topological-sort/1",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/5lZ0iJMrUMk",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/33bapUo",
    topicNo: 22,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_161",
    problem: "Number of islands(Do in Grid and Graph Both)",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/number-of-islands/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/muncqlKJrH0",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3KaSCND",
    topicNo: 22,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_162",
    problem: "Bipartite Check using BFS",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/is-graph-bipartite/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/-vu34sct1g8",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3tps98W",
    topicNo: 22,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_163",
    problem: "Bipartite Check using DFS",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/is-graph-bipartite/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/KG5YFfR0j8A",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3tps98W",
    topicNo: 22,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_164",
    problem: "Strongly Connected Component(using KosaRaju’s algo)",
    leetCode:
      "https://leetcode.com/problems/maximum-number-of-non-overlapping-substrings/discuss/766485/kosaraju-algorithm-on",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/V8qIqJxCioo",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3twUKJP",
    topicNo: 23,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_165",
    problem: "Dijkstra’s Algorithm",
    leetCode:
      "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/implementing-dijkstra-set-1-adjacency-matrix/1",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/rp1SMw7HSO8",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3qrEHLm",
    topicNo: 23,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_166",
    problem: "Bellman-Ford Algo",
    leetCode:
      "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/distance-from-the-source-bellman-ford-algorithm/0/?fbclid=IwAR2_lL0T84DnciLyzMTQuVTMBOi82nTWNLuXjUgahnrtBgkphKiYk6xcyJU",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/0vVofAhAYjc",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3GwAf3A",
    topicNo: 23,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_167",
    problem: "Floyd Warshall Algorithm",
    leetCode:
      "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/implementing-floyd-warshall2042/1",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/YbY8cVwWAvw",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3Kb41Ny",
    topicNo: 23,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_168",
    problem: "MST using Prim’s Algo",
    leetCode:
      "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/minimum-spanning-tree/1",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/mJcZjjKzeqk",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3I5Ktbi",
    topicNo: 23,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_169",
    problem: "MST using Kruskal’s Algo",
    leetCode:
      "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/minimum-spanning-tree/1",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/1KRmCzBl_mQ",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3I1VqL9",
    topicNo: 23,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_170",
    problem: "Max Product Subarray",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/maximum-product-subarray/",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3fqz6OS",
    topicNo: 24,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_171",
    problem: "Longest Increasing Subsequence",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/longest-increasing-subsequence/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/ekcwMsSIzVc}",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3GuWGpA",
    topicNo: 24,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_172",
    problem: "Longest Common Subsequence",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/longest-common-subsequence/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/NPZn9jBrX8U}",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3raZbqM",
    topicNo: 24,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_173",
    problem: "0-1 Knapsack",
    leetCode:
      "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/0-1-knapsack-problem0945/1",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/GqOmJHQZivw}",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3FvHbMO",
    topicNo: 24,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_174",
    problem: "Edit Distance",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/edit-distance/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/fJaKO8FbDdo}",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3qpUHgE",
    topicNo: 24,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_175",
    problem: "Maximum sum increasing subsequence",
    leetCode:
      "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/maximum-sum-increasing-subsequence4749/1",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3tqiS0s",
    topicNo: 24,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_176",
    problem: "Matrix Chain Multiplication",
    leetCode:
      "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/matrix-chain-multiplication0303/1",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/vRVfmbCFW7Y}",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3qqX56T",
    topicNo: 24,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_177",
    problem:
      "Minimum sum path in the matrix, (count paths and similar type do, also backtrack to find the Minimum path)",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/minimum-path-sum/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/_rgTlyky1uQ}",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3zWJEin",
    topicNo: 25,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_178",
    problem: "Coin change",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/coin-change/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/HgyouUi11zk}",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3GwBrnA",
    topicNo: 25,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_179",
    problem: "Subset Sum",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/partition-equal-subset-sum/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/fWX9xDmIzRI",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3rjUdb7",
    topicNo: 25,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_180",
    problem: "Rod Cutting",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/minimum-cost-to-cut-a-stick/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/mO8XpGoJwuo}",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3GuIsoS",
    topicNo: 25,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_181",
    problem: "Egg Dropping",
    leetCode:
      "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/egg-dropping-puzzle-1587115620/1",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3A6id5O",
    topicNo: 25,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_182",
    problem: "Word Break",
    leetCode: "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/word-break1352/1",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3npqs7P",
    topicNo: 25,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_183",
    problem: "Palindrome Partitioning (MCM Variation)",
    leetCode:
      "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/palindromic-patitioning4845/1",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/_H8V5hJUGd0}",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3tq9MRn",
    topicNo: 25,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_184",
    problem: "Maximum profit in Job scheduling",
    leetCode:
      "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/job-sequencing-problem-1587115620/1",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/34FoY2C",
    topicNo: 25,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_185",
    problem: "Implement Trie (Prefix Tree)",
    leetCode: "https://leetcode.com/problems/implement-trie-prefix-tree/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/dBGUmUQhjaM",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/33wIn5x",
    topicNo: 26,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_186",
    problem: "Implement Trie – 2 (Prefix Tree)",
    leetCode: "https://bit.ly/3qwT4OL",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/K5pcpkEMCN0",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3I8Q9l7",
    topicNo: 26,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_187",
    problem: "Longest String with All Prefixes",
    leetCode: "https://bit.ly/3n3kedU",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/AWnBa91lThI",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3qrU6vb",
    topicNo: 26,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_188",
    problem: "Number of Distinct Substrings in a String",
    leetCode: "https://bit.ly/3ocRQW0",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/RV0QeTyHZxo",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3zVV1XD",
    topicNo: 26,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_189",
    problem: "Power Set (this is very important)",
    leetCode: "https://practice.geeksforgeeks.org/problems/power-set4302/1#",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/b7AYbpM5YrE",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3fmd28k",
    topicNo: 26,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_190",
    problem: "Maximum XOR of two numbers in an array",
    leetCode:
      "https://leetcode.com/problems/maximum-xor-of-two-numbers-in-an-array/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/EIhAwfHubE8",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3rjEYis",
    topicNo: 26,
  },
  {
    checkbox: "ques_191",
    problem: "Maximum XOR With an Element From Array",
    leetCode:
      "https://leetcode.com/problems/maximum-xor-with-an-element-from-array/",
    videoSolution: "https://youtube.com/embed/Q8LhG9Pi5KM",
    codingNinja: "https://bit.ly/3KbHhN4",
    topicNo: 26,
  },
] as {
  checkbox: string;
  problem: string;
  leetCode: string;
  videoSolution?: string;
  codingNinja: string;
  topicNo: number;
}[];
export const ssTopics = [
  "Arrays",
  "Arrays Part-II",
  "Arrays Part-III",
  "Arrays Part-IV",
  "Linked List",
  "Linked List Part-II",
  "Linked List and Arrays",
  "Greedy Algorithm",
  "Recursion ",
  "Recursion and Backtracking",
  "Binary Search",
  "Heaps",
  "Stack and Queue",
  "Stack and Queue Part-II",
  "String",
  "String Part-II",
  "Binary Tree",
  "Binary Tree part-II",
  "Binary Tree part-III",
  "Binary Search Tree",
  "Binary Search Tree Part-II",
  "Binary Trees[Miscellaneous]",
  "Graph",
  "Graph Part-II",
  "Dynamic Programming",
  "Dynamic Programming Part-II",
  "Trie",
] as string[];
export const ssCount = [
  6, 6, 6, 6, 6, 6, 6, 6, 6, 6, 8, 6, 7, 10, 6, 6, 12, 8, 7, 7, 8, 6, 12, 6, 7,
  8, 7,
] as number[];
